http://www.bitsandpiecesuk.com/privacy_and_security/

Satisfaction Guaranteed! Order online or call 8-8, Mon-Fri and 9-5, Weekends: 0871 472 4277
Call costs 13p per minute plus access charge.
Sign In
COVID-19 UPDATE: Due to strict social distancing measures at our fulfilment centre, our delivery times are longer than usual. Thank you for your patience.
MENU
Search
Help
0
Close
Shopping Cart
0 Items
Subtotal: £0
Continue Shopping
Checkout »
1.871.472.4277
Product
Quantity
Price
0 Items in Basket
My Basket
0 items   £0
UNIQUE GIFTS
About Us
The Bits And Pieces UK website is owned and operated by Kafka UK Direct Limited, Wadsworth Road, Kelleythorpe Industrial Estate, Driffied, YO25 9DJ.
If you need to contact us, please email. Alternatively you can call us using the following telephone numbers:
For order line telephone 0871 472 4277 (calls cost 13p per minute plus your phone company's access charge.)
For enquiries related to Customer Service, please call 0871 472 4266.
VAT number: 922979289
Company registration number: 6609907
Making a Contract with Us
When you place an order with us, you are making an offer to buy goods. We will send you an e-mail to confirm that we have received and accept your order, and that a contract has been made between us.
In the unlikely event that the goods are no longer available, we may provide you with a refund or supply you with substitute goods. If you decide not to accept the substitute goods, you will not have to pay to return them to us.
When you place an order with us we automatically add you to our subscriber list for our e-mail campaigns. This is so you can be aware of our latest offers and exclusive deals. If you do not wish to receive e-mails then please email.
Delivery
Our 'Standard' delivery is £4.99 no matter how large your order.
Standard delivery is available to all UK addresses including Northern Ireland, Isle of Man, Scilly Isles and the Channel Islands.
Orders are dispatched via our couriers 'Hermes' usually within 72 hours and normally delivered to your door within 7-14 days from date of placing. We offer free delivery insurance covering your parcel for loss or damage during transit.
We regret we are currently unable to deliver any service to Eire.
Any problems at all with your delivery, please contact us in the first instance 0871 472 4266.
Cancellation and Returns
You can cancel your contract at any time up to 14 working days after the day of delivery. Under the Consumer Contracts (Information, Additional Charges & Cancellation) Regulations 2013 you have a 14 day period following the day after delivery in which to cancel this contract. To do this, please email us or write to us at: Bits And Pieces, PO Box 98, Driffield, YO25 9DJ.
You do not have to give any reason for cancellation. However, a brief explanation will help us to improve the service we offer to customers in the future.
If you cancel, you must return the goods to us at your own expense. You must ensure that the goods are packaged adequately to protect against damage.
If you fail to take reasonable care of goods before they are returned to us, and this results in damage or deterioration, we will charge you for the reduction in value.
Please be aware returns can take up to 28 days to complete processing.
This cancellation policy does not affect your legal rights - for example, if goods are faulty or misdescribed.
Faulty Goods
If there is a problem with the goods, please contact us. We will deal with the matter in accordance with your legal rights.
Privacy Policy
General
Terms and expressions used in this Privacy Policy bear the same meaning as in our Terms and Conditions.
Bits And Pieces UK respects the privacy of the users of our Services and Website.
We adhere to a strict "no-spam" policy, meaning that you must sign up for one of our Services or request information from us before you receive any e-mail communication from us.
This Privacy Policy explains how we use the personal data we collect about you, how you can instruct us if you prefer to limit the use of that data and procedures that we have in place to safeguard your privacy.
We apply the data protection principles found in the Data Protection Act 1998 ("the Act").
Collection of Data from our Clients
In order for us to process your order we may require some standard information from you such as your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number and telephone number.
The relevant data is then used by us to communicate with you on any matter relating to your account. Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of your identity before we are able to disclose personal data to you.
We may also use aggregate data and statistics for the purposes of monitoring website usage in order to help us develop our Website may provide such aggregate data to third parties. These statistics will not include data that can be used to identify any individual.
It is Our Policy that Your Data is Private and Confidential
The personal data you provide to us is treated by us as private and confidential and is stored by us in a secure location, is accessible only by designated staff, and is used only for the purposes for which you provide the data. When you submit an order, your data is encrypted with secure server software to protect the data from unauthorized access.
We may disclose personal data in the following circumstances:
to the extent that it is available through the provision of our Services (notwithstanding that phone numbers, fax numbers, email addresses and postal addresses are not disclosed)
to comply with a court order; if we believe in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to identify persons violating the law.
If such disclosure is required under or authorized by law (to police, trading standards units, HM Customs and Revenue, the Office of Fair Trading and other law enforcement bodies that require the data for their investigations;) and other third parties with valid reasons under the Act.
Your Rights
You have various rights under the Act, including upon a written request to us, to receive a description of the personal data held by us of which you are subject, the purpose for which the data is processed and the third parties or class of third parties to whom the data may be disclosed.
If you would like to stop all unsolicited postal communications, we suggest that you register with the Mailing Preference Service (MPS). MPS is a free service set up in 1983 and funded by the direct mail industry to enable consumers to have their names and home addresses in the UK removed from lists used by the industry. It is actively supported by the Royal Mail and all directly involved trade associations and fully supported by The Information Commissioners Office (ICO). For more information or if you wish to register with the MPS please visit their website www.mpsonline.org.uk
Computer Tracking of Identifiable Data
Our Web site tracks data about the visits to our Website. This enables us to compile statistics that show the daily number of visitors to the Website, the daily requests we receive for particular files on our Web site, and what countries those requests come from. These aggregated statistics may be used internally to better provide services to our customers but will not be disclosed to third parties save as provided in this Privacy Policy.
Third Party Targeting Cookies or Advertising Cookies
These cookies are used to deliver adverts more relevant to you and your interests. They are also used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement as well as help measure the effectiveness of the advertising campaign. These cookies are placed by advertising networks with our permission. They remember that you have visited a website and this information is shared with other organisations such as advertisers. Quite often targeting or advertising cookies will be linked to site functionality provided by the other organisations.
The only time these cookies would enable us to share personal information such as your name, address, telephone or email is when you have given consent for your personal information to be passed on to trusted third parties.
Our communications are designed to tell you about the benefits we can offer so that you have access to our best deals. We use the information we have about you to tailor the content and try to ensure that the offers are as relevant to you as possible. Under the Data Protection Legislation, this might qualify as profiling. If you do not wish us to use your data for this purpose, please call on 0871 472 4266, write to us at Bits And Pieces, Wadsworth Road, Kelleythorpe Industrial Estate, Driffield, YO25 9DJ or email us at customerserviceuk@bitsandpieces.com
We may share data (Name & Address only) with other carefully selected retail companies and charities who we feel may be of interest to you. If data is shared it is done so on a one time only basis and the company or organisation are not entitled to store your data for further use unless you engage with them.
We also work with Epsilon Abacus (registered as Epsilon International UK Ltd), a company that manages the Abacus Alliance on behalf of UK retailers. The participating retailers are active in the following product categories: clothing, collectables, food & wine, gardening, gadgets & entertainment, health & beauty, household goods, and home interiors. They share information on what their customers buy. Epsilon Abacus analyses this pooled information to help retailers understand consumers' wider buying patterns. From this information, retailers can tailor their communications, sending people suitable offers that should be of interest to them, based on what they like to buy.
Please note that Epsilon Abacus may transfer data outside the EEA. The transfer will take place in the presence of appropriate safeguards, including standard data protection clauses adopted by the EU Commission. If you would like more information, please call us on 0871 472 4266, or write to us at our address below or email us at customerserviceuk@bitsandpieces.com
To find new customers for our business we are a member of a co-operative of UK retail brands that pool and share transactional information. We work with a Company called Conexance that processes customer transactional data on behalf of each Member. This process highlights spending patterns and allows us to identify suitable prospects to receive an introduction from us via the post. Thus, we send offers and information only to prospective customers that are likely to be interested in buying from us. Co-op Member brands operate in numerous categories, including apparel, home and garden, collectables, food and wine, gadgets and gifts, entertainment, health and beauty, travel and leisure. If you would rather your information was not included in this processing just email customerserviceuk@bitsandpieces.com and we will ensure it is not shared for the purpose above.
If you do not wish us to share this information please update this preference at any time by calling us on 0871 472 4266, write to us at Bits And Pieces, Wadsworth Road, Kelleythorpe Industrial Estate, Driffield, YO25 9DJ.
Updating Your Details
We are committed to maintaining accurate, timely, relevant and appropriate information about our customers. If any of the data that you have provided to Bits And Pieces UK changes, for example if you change your email address, name or payment details or if you wish to cancel your subscription please let us know the correct details by sending an email.
Updates and Special Offers
We may occasionally notify you of new services and special offers via e-mail or postal mail. If you would rather not receive any updates from us, please send a request to opt-out of receiving these promotional mailings by sending an email.
Your Consent
By submitting your data you consent to the collection and use of data as set forth above. Bits And Pieces UK reserves the right to change this policy at any time, any changes to our Privacy Policy will be posted to the Bits And Pieces UK Web sites so that you may be aware of the data we collect and how we use it at all times and so that you may consent to our use of your data in that way. Continued use of our Services will signify that you agree to any such changes.
How to Contact Bits And Pieces
We welcome your views about our Website and our Privacy Policy. If you would like to contact us with any queries or comments please send an email.
Sign up to receive exclusive promotions & product collections from Bits and Pieces.
Subscribe Now
Bits and Pieces
Wadsworth Road
Kelleythorpe Ind Est Driffield
YO25 9DJ
Comodo SSL
Quick Menu
Home
Social Media
Want Our New Catalogue?
Get Our Latest Catalogue with many new arrivals. Shop new puzzles, home and garden arrivals, seasonal sales and clearance now.
Request
Quick Menu
Home
About Us
Contact Us
Shipping & Returns
My Account
Privacy & Security
Social Media
Want Our New Catalogue?
© Copyright 2020 Bits And Pieces UK. All Rights Reserved.
Order online or call 8-8, Mon-Fri and 9-5, Weekends: 0871 472 4277 Call costs 13p per minute plus network extras.
We use cookies to make your experience better. To comply with the new e-Privacy directive, we need to ask for your consent to set the cookies. Learn more Allow Cookies
Sign In
Request Free Catalogue
Products Categories
Unique Gifts
All Unique Gifts
3D Puzzles
Apparel
Banks & Money Holders
